Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - Cataloged individually
        - Party up in here, 1979; SR-7466; Brides of Funkenstein (Musical group) (Box 11)
          Promotional copy. From the Atlantic LP 19261 - Never buy Texas from a cowboy.
        - All American masher, 1981; SR-7499; Bolins, Chet. (Box 11)
          Disc pressed on red vinyl..
          Straight-Face
          Newark, Deleware
        - Bombers., 1978; SR-7500; Bombers (Disco group) (Box 11)
          West End Records
        - Megablast; Don't make me wait, 1988; SR-7501; Bomb the Bass, 1968- (Box 11)
          Red and green labels.
          Rhythm King Music
        - (Everbody) get dancin'; Don't stop the music., 1979; SR-7502; Bombers (Disco group) (Box 11)
        - Collection. Volume 2, 2000; SR-7503-7504; Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) (Box 11)
          Ruthless Records
        - New funky nation, 1990; SR-7508-7509; Boo-Yaa T.R.I.B.E. (Musical group) (Box 11)
          4th & B'way
        - Romeo Knight, 1988; SR-7510; Boogie Boys. (Box 11)
        - Survival of the freshest, 1986; SR-7511; Boogie Boys. (Box 11)
        - Survival of the freshest, 1986; SR-7512; Boogie Boys. (Box 11)
        - Booker T. & the M.G.'s greatest hits, 1980; SR-7513 (Box 11)
          Stax Records
        - Booker T. & the M.G.'s greatest hits, 1970; SR-7514 (Box 11)
          Memphis, Tennessee
        - See jungle! see jungle! go join your gang yeah! city all over, go ape crazy., 1981; SR-7515 (Box 11)
        - Last of the Mohicans, 1982; SR-7516; Bow Wow Wow (Musical group) (Box 11)
        - I wanna feel your love; Since I found you (love is better than ever), 1981; SR-7517; Bowman, Californiandy. (Box 11)
          RCA: JD-12305; additional no.: PD-12305.
        - Blockbusters, 1987; SR-7518; Boys on the Block (Musical group) (Box 11)
        - Messages from the Boys, 1988; SR-7519; Boys (Musical group) (Box 11)
          Motown Records
        - Strawberries & cream, 1996; SR-7520-7521; Boutique (Musical group) (Box 11)
          Trade 2
        - Fame 90, 1990; SR-7522-7523; Bowie, David. (Box 11)
          Matrix / Runout (Etched, Runout Groove, Side A): V-1-56163-Z1-DMM SP1-1; Matrix / Runout (Etched, Runout Groove, Side B): V-2-56163-Z1-DMM SP1-1.
        - You can do it, 1997; SR-7524-7525; Brand New Heavies (Musical group) (Box 11)
          Delicious Vinyl
        - Sittin' up in my room: remix, 1996; SR-7527-7528; Brandy, 1979- (Box 11)
          Arista Records
        - Brand New Heavies: featuring N'Dea Davenport, 1991; SR-7529-7530; Brand New Heavies (Musical group) (Box 11)
          Delabel
        - Conversations., 1983; SR-7531; Brass Construction (Musical group) (Box 11)
        - Conquest, 1985; SR-7532; Muller, Randy. (Box 11)
        - Attitude, 1982; SR-7533; Brass Construction (Musical group) (Box 11)
          Lester Radio Corp.
        - Brass construction VI., 1980; SR-7534; Brass Construction (Musical group) (Box 11)
          Liberty
        - After 5, 1982; SR-7535; Brick (Musical group) (Box 11)
          Bang Records; Distributed by CBS Records
        - Do good and live, 1981; SR-7536; Brigo. (Box 11)
        - Ekambi Brillant., 1981; SR-7537; Brillant, Ekambi. (Box 11)
          Jay-Walking
        - I love you more and more, 1974; SR-7538; Brock, Tom. (Box 11)
          20th Century Fox Records
        - United chair., 1973; SR-7539 (Box 11)
          Today
        - Drums; Go away, 1981; SR-7542; Brooks, Dianne. (Box 11)
          Town House
        - Chillin' out, 1981; SR-7543-7544; Brooks, Inez. (Box 11)
        - We all know who we are, 1977; SR-7169; Cameo (Musical group) (Box 12)
          "Promotional copy."
          Chocolate City
        - This is Billy Butler., 1969; SR-7403; Butler, Billy. (Box 12)
        - Cool breeze., 1972; SR-7464; Burke, Solomon. (Box 12)
          MGM
        - Mellow days & funny nites; Laid back, 1980-1989; SR-7465; Brutus (Musician) (Box 12)
          Nemperor Records
        - Eric Brouta., 1989; SR-7540; Brouta, Eric. (Box 12)
          Little Star Records
        - Party girl, 1979; SR-7541; Brooks, Pattie. (Box 12)
        - Pattie Brooks., 1980; SR-7545 (Box 12)
        - Elementalz, 1996; SR-7546-7547; Brotherhood (Hip hop group) (Box 12)
          Bite It! Recordings: Virgin
        - Winners, 1981; SR-7553; Brothers Johnson. (Box 12)
        - Brother 2 Brother, 1980; SR-7554; Brother to Brother (Soul group) (Box 12)
          Sugar Hill Records
        - Blam!!, 1978; SR-7555; Brothers Johnson. (Box 12)
        - Stargazer, 1979; SR-7556; Brown, Peter, 1953- (Box 12)
          Drive
        - Fantasy love affair, 1977; SR-7557; Brown, Peter, 1953- (Box 12)
          Dream Records
        - You've got to like what you do, 1980; SR-7558; Brown, Shirley, 1947- (Box 12)
          Promotional/DJ copy.
        - Just like that, 1988; SR-7559; Brownmark (Musician) (Box 12)
          Detroit, Michigan
        - Magic, 1981; SR-7560; Browne, Tom (Trumpet player) (Box 12)
        - Bobby, 1992; SR-7561-7562; Brown, Bobby (Vocalist) (Box 12)
        - Two can play that game, 1995; SR-7563-7564; Brown, Bobby (Vocalist) (Box 12)
        - Songs from the Broadway production of "The Catherine wheel", 1981; SR-7565; Byrne, David, 1952- (Box 12)
        - Everybody in the house, 1995; SR-7566; Buzzthrill (Musical group) (Box 12)
          Jupiter Records Inc.
          California
        - Melinda original music from the motion picture. all selections written by Jerry Butler and Jerry Peters., 1972; SR-7567; Butler, Jerry. (Box 12)
          Prestige Records: Distributed by Fantasy Records
        - Money don't make no man, 1988; SR-7568; O'Neal, Brian. (Box 12)
          Voss Records
          Oxnard, California
        - We want it all, 1989; SR-7569; Butter Rum (Musical group) (Box 12)
        - Best belong together, 1988; SR-7570; B.V.S.M.P. (Musical group) (Box 12)
          BCM Records
        - Best belong together, 1988; SR-7571; B.V.S.M.P. (Musical group) (Box 12)
          Dave Crawford Productions
        - Love byrd, 1981; SR-7572; Byrd, Donald. (Box 12)
          Electric Cat
        - On the move (I can't get enough), 1993; SR-7573; Byrd, Bobby, 1934-2007. (Box 12)
          Soulciety Records
        - Back to the old school, 1999; SR-7574; Busta Funk (Musician) (Box 12)
          Funky Delicacies
        - Dig, 1991; SR-7575; Burning Flames (Musical group) (Box 12)
        - Farover, 1987; SR-7576; Burning Spear, 1948- (Box 12)
          HDM
        - Offlanders; Slick turf, 2000; SR-7577; Burner Brothers. (Box 12)
          Rawkuts
        - In black and white, 1983; SR-7578; Burton, Jenny. (Box 12)
        - Playing hard to get, 1982; SR-7579; Burch, Vernon. (Box 12)
          SRI
          Coral Gables, Fla.
        - Steppin' out, 1980; SR-7580; Burch, Vernon. (Box 12)
          Promotional copy; not for sale.
        - Running thangs, 1988; SR-7581-7582; Busy Bee. (Box 12)
        - When disaster strikes--, 1997; SR-7583-7584; Busta Rhymes (Musician) (Box 12)
          "For promotional use only. Not for sale."
        - Pac-man fever, 1982; SR-7586; Buckner & Garcia. (Box 12)
        - Peabo, 1976; SR-7587; Bryson, Peabo, (Box 12)
          Bullet Records
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - Fresh, 1984; SR-7588; Brunson, Tyrone. (Box 12)
          Believe in a Dream Records
        - Sticky situation, 1983; SR-7589; Brunson, Tyrone, (Box 12)
        - Love triangle, 1987; SR-7590-7591; Brunson, Tyrone. (Box 12)
        - Greatest hits, 1980; SR-7592; B.T. Express (Musical group) (Box 12)
        - That's how love is., 1989; SR-7593 (Box 12)
          WEA
        - Jet Brown., 1979; SR-7594; Brown, Jet. (Box 12)
        - Sirround sound, 2002; SR-7595-7596; Brown, DjiNew Jerseyi. (Box 12)
          7Heads Recordings
        - Ain't it funky, 1990-1999; SR-7597; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 12)
        - Jimmy Castor story: "from the roots", 1973; SR-6948; Jimmy Castor Bunch. (Box 13)
          Paul Winley Records
        - Mas fever, 1978; SR-6955; Calypso Rose. (Box 13)
          CLO Records
          Port of Spain, Trinidad and Tobago
        - Supersound, 1975; SR-6964; Jimmy Castor Bunch. (Box 13)
          "Promotional DJ copy, not for sale"
        - Return of Leroy, 1983; SR-7054; Castor, Jimmy. (Box 13)
          Douglas/Casablanca Records & Filmworks
        - Caress, 1977; SR-7119; Caress (Musical group) (Box 13)
          Panchin Pub. Inc.: Mfg. by Pantera Prod.
        - It's serious, 1977; SR-7168; Cameo (Musical group) (Box 13)
          Promotional DJ copy recorded on one side only.
        - Was that all it was; What's on your mind, 1979; SR-7172-7173; Carne, Jean. (Box 13)
          Philadelphia International Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Dr. Rock, 1979; SR-7190-7191; Captain Sky. (Box 13)
          AVI Records
        - This must be heaven., 1981; SR-7216 (Box 13)
          Cherie Records
          Birmingham, Michigan
        - This must be heaven., 1981; SR-7217; Carr, Jerry. (Box 13)
        - Get down attack, 1980; SR-7244-7245; General Caine (Musical group) (Box 13)
          Groove Production
        - Super rock body shock, 1980-1989; SR-7249; Eye Beta Rock (Musician) (Box 13)
          "Promotional copy--not for sale."
          H&L Records
          Englewood Cliffs, New Jersey
        - Sensuous black woman meets the sensuous black man, 1972; SR-7251; Moore, Rudy Ray, 1927-2008. (Box 13)
          Kenellie
        - Must be the music, 1981; SR-7253 (Box 13)
        - Bobby Caldwell., 1978; SR-7490-7491; Caldwell, Bobby. (Box 13)
          Clouds
        - Cameosis, 1980; SR-7492-7493; Cameo (Musical group) (Box 13)
        - (I'll be your) piece of the rock; Love recession, 1982; SR-7598; Carr, Jerry, 1955- (Box 13)
        - Hoodoo voodoo, 1979; SR-7608; C.D. Band. (Box 13)
          Casabalanca Record and FilmWorks
        - Alternating currents, 1978; SR-7609; Celi Bee. (Box 13)
          APA
        - Cee-Lo Green-- is the soul machine., 2004; SR-7621-7622; Cee-Lo (Musician) (Box 13)
        - Unbelievable, 1978; SR-7628; Paul Cacia Big Band. (Box 13)
          Alexander Street Records
          Sherman Oaks, California
        - Time and chance, 1978; SR-7629; Caldera (Musical group) (Box 13)
        - Cameron., 1980; SR-7630; Cameron, Rafael. (Box 13)
        - Soul strike!, 2001; SR-7631-7632; Calypso King & The Soul Investigators (Musical group) (Box 13)
        - Can't tempt fate, 1985; SR-7639; Circuit II (Musical group) (Box 13)
        - Machismo, 1988; SR-7640; Cameo (Musical group) (Box 13)
          Atlanta Artists 422 836 002-1 (on container: 836 002-1).
          Atlanta Artists: Manufactured and marketed by Polygram
        - Real men ... wear black, 1990; SR-7641; Cameo (Musical group) (Box 13)
          Atlanta Artists 422 846 297-1 (on container: 846 297-1).
          Atlanta Artists
        - She's strange, 1984; SR-7642; Cameo (Musical group) (Box 13)
        - Style, 1983; SR-7643; Cameo (Musical group) (Box 13)
          Polydor/Kolob Records
        - Slow movin', 1983; SR-7644; Cameo (Musical group) (Box 13)
        - 357; Pull it, 1998; SR-7645; Cam'Ron. (Box 13)
        - Dancin' and prancin', 1979; SR-7646; Candido, 1921- (Box 13)
        - Made in America, 1981; SR-7647; Carpenters (Musical group) (Box 13)
        - Jean Carn., 1976; SR-7648; Carne, Jean. (Box 13)
          PhD Records and Tapes
        - Honey, 1997; SR-7649-7650; Carey, Mariah. (Box 13)
        - Porter Carroll, II., 1986; SR-7653; Carroll, Porter. (Box 13)
          Island: 7 90506-1 (on container).
        - Onda; Central do Brasil, 2014; SR-7654; Cassiano, 1943- (Box 13)
        - Get down; Flowing inside, 1982; SR-7655; Case, Connie. (Box 13)
          Koala/Silver Bear
          Hendersonville, Tennessee
        - Eyes of the mind., 1981; SR-7656; Casiopea (Musical group) (Box 13)
          Alfa Records
        - Cashflow., 1986; SR-7657; Cashflow (Musical group) (Box 13)
        - Caveman., 1990; SR-7658; Caveman (Musical group) (Box 13)
        - Hummin', 1996; SR-7659; Cannonball Adderley Quintet. (Box 13)
          Blue Note
        - Capital tropical, 1981; SR-7660; Two Man Sound (Musical group) (Box 13)
          TSR Records
        - Love letters; I got to sing, 1981; SR-7661; Caprice (Musical group) (Box 13)
          Beggars Banquet
        - Christmasing, 1986; SR-7662; Caesar, Shirley, 1938- (Box 13)
          Rejoice; Distributed by A & M Records
          Waco, Texas
        - Percolator, 1992; SR-7663; Green Velvet, 1968- (Box 13)
          Cajual Records
        - Artificial intelligence, 1985; SR-7664; Cale, John. (Box 13)
        - Take it down low; Blue laser, 2001; SR-7666; Capone. (Box 13)
          Handshake Records
        - Hangin', 1982; SR-6988; Edwards, Bernard, 1952-1996, (Box 14)
        - Gavin., 1988; SR-6993; Christopher, Gavin. (Box 14)
          EMI America
        - Life: with The Fanatic remix, 1997; SR-6994 (Box 14)
          Select Records
        - Hipnotism, 1980; SR-6996; Chocolate Milk (Musical group) (Box 14)
        - Comin', 1976; SR-6997; Chocolate Milk (Musical group) (Box 14)
        - Stop what you're doin', 1984; SR-7000; Chi-Lites (Musical group), (Box 14)
          Prism
        - Baby let's do it the French way, 1977; SR-7001; Chocolat's (Musical group) (Box 14)
          Able Records
        - Real people, 1980; SR-7002; Chic (Musical group), (Box 14)
        - Blue jeans; Dawn, 1981; SR-7004; Chocolate Milk (Musical group) (Box 14)
        - Glow of love, 1980; SR-7011; Change (Musical group) (Box 14)
          Warner Brothers Records/RFC
        - Ya bad Chubbs, 1989; SR-7019-7020; Rock, Chubb, (Box 14)
        - Clash., 1979; SR-7053 (Box 14)
        - New generation, 1971; SR-7154-7155; Chambers Brothers. (Box 14)
        - London calling, 1979; SR-7214-7215; Clash (Musical group) (Box 14)
        - B-sides, sessions & rarities, 2002; SR-7606-7607; Certain Ratio (Musical group) (Box 14)
          Soul Jazz Records
        - If my friends could see me now., 1978; SR-7610 (Box 14)
          Curtom Records
        - Right combination., 1980; SR-7611; Clifford, Linda (Vocalist) (Box 14)
        - Here's my love., 1979; SR-7612; Clifford, Linda (Vocalist) (Box 14)
        - I'm yours, 1980; SR-7613; Clifford, Linda (Vocalist) (Box 14)
        - Clarke, 1981; SR-7614; Clarke, Stanley. (Box 14)
        - Power and the glory, 1983; SR-7615; Cliff, Jimmy. (Box 14)
        - We all are one, 1983; SR-7616; Cliff, Jimmy. (Box 14)
        - Sandinista!, 1980; SR-7617-7619; Clash (Musical group) (Box 14)
        - Tracy Chapman., 1988; SR-7623; Chapman, Tracy, 1964- (Box 14)
        - Don Cherry., 1975; SR-7624; Cherry, Don. (Box 14)
          Honeybee Records
        - Streetcar named Desire, 1982; SR-7625; Cherry, Ava. (Box 14)
        - Modern man., 1978; SR-7626; Clarke, Stanley. (Box 14)
          NCI
        - Lover's holiday, 1980; SR-7634; Change (Musical group) (Box 14)
          Promotional copy. Single sided recording from the Warner / RFC album 3438, The glow of love.
        - Chameleon., 1979; SR-7636-7637; Chameleon (Soul group) (Box 14)
          Promo copy for radio station use only.
        - When you're #1, 1979; SR-7638; Chandler, Gene, (Box 14)
        - Can you feel it; While we still have time, 1979; SR-7651; Cindy & Roy. (Box 14)
          Casablanca Records
        - Some of my best jokes are friends, 1985; SR-7667; Clinton, George, 1940- (Box 14)
        - R & B skeletons (in the closet), 1986; SR-7668; Clinton, George, 1940- (Box 14)
        - T.A.P.O.A.F.O.M.: the awesome power of a fully-operational mothership, 1996; SR-7669; Clinton, George, 1940- (Box 14)
          Sony Music
        - 500,000 kilowatts of P-funk power, 2004; SR-7670-7672; Clinton, George, 1940- (Box 14)
          Generation Records
          St. Laurent, Quebec
        - Surrender (your love), 1990; SR-7673; Clear Touch (Musical group) (Box 14)
          MGM/Kolob Records
        - Ling-O-istic; It's time to jam, 1988; SR-7674; Cli-n-Tel (Musical group) (Box 14)
          Sutra Records
        - Third World child, 1987; SR-7676; Clegg, Johnny, 1953- (Box 14)
        - Third World child, 1987; SR-7677; Clegg, Johnny, 1953- (Box 14)
        - T.A.P.O.A.F.O.M.: the awesome power of a fully-operational mothership, 1996; SR-7786; Clinton, George, 1940- (Box 14)
        - Take a lickin' and keep on kickin', 1982; SR-6942; Collins, Bootsy. (Box 15)
        - Nothing ever changes, 1983; SR-6975; Cosmic Touch (Musical group) (Box 15)
          Serious Gold
        - Here am I, 1975; SR-7059; Crawford, Dave. (Box 15)
          Dash
        - Sound of young New York., 1983; SR-7066-7067 (Box 15)
          CBS Associated Records
        - Guyane ma ne¿¿gresse, 1980-1989; SR-7108; Cyrille, Henri, (Box 15)
          Tabata Music; Distributed by Musique Music
          Guyane
        - Black motion picture experience., 1973; SR-7208-7209 (Box 15)
        - Phantasy eyeland (what is your phantasy); What is your phantasy (phantasy eyeland), 1981; SR-7331; Adventure (Musical group) (Box 15)
          Heartbeat Records
          Somerville, Massachusetts
        - Life:styles, 2004; SR-7467-7468 (Box 15)
          Hardleaders
        - Bayou country, 1969; SR-7472; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Musical group) (Box 15)
        - So in luv, 1996; SR-7475; Collision (Musical group) (Box 15)
          Chansons Records
        - Got to keep on, 1989; SR-7476; Cookie Crew (Musical group) (Box 15)
          Fashion Fair Music: White Diamond Records
          Hempstead, New York
        - Burnin' love, 1986; SR-7477; Con-Funk-Shun (Musical group) (Box 15)
        - Touch, 1980; SR-7480; Con-Funk-Shun (Musical group) (Box 15)
        - Too tight, 1980; SR-7481; Con-Funk-Shun (Musical group) (Box 15)
        - Electric lady, 1985; SR-7482; Con-Funk-Shun (Musical group) (Box 15)
        - Best of Norman Connors & friends., 1978; SR-7483 (Box 15)
        - Loveshine, 1978; SR-7484; Con-Funk-Shun (Musical group) (Box 15)
        - Fill your life with love, 1978; SR-7485; Controllers (Musical group) (Box 15)
          Josie
        - Mr. C, 1981; SR-7486; Connors, Norman. (Box 15)
        - Wie war das nach mal? = (Back in the old days), 1996; SR-7487; Coolen Sa¿¿ue (Musical group) (Box 15)
          Ariola
        - Dreamworld, 1972; SR-7488; Continental Four (Musical group) (Box 15)
          Janus Records
        - Stay, 1986; SR-7489; Controllers (Musical group) (Box 15)
          Netherlands
        - Give it to me (if you don't mind), 1981; SR-7494; Conquest (Musical group) (Box 15)
        - We like your lovin', 1987; SR-7495; Colors 'n' Between (Musical group) (Box 15)
          Musicworks
        - Bootsy? Player of the year, 1978; SR-7505; Bootsy's Rubber Band. (Box 15)
        - Blasters' of the universe, 1993; SR-7506; Bootsy's New Rubber Band. (Box 15)
          P-Vine Records
          Japan
        - Love will bring us back together, 1991; SR-7599; Cookie Crew (Musical group) (Box 15)
          FFRR
        - Face value, 1981; SR-7604; Collins, Phil. (Box 15)
        - Tiempo pa' matar, 1984; SR-7605; Colo¿¿n, Willie, 1950- (Box 15)
          Fania Records
        - Life, love & pain, 1986; SR-7627; Club Nouveau (Musical group) (Box 15)
          Promotional copy.Warner Bros.: 1-25531 (on container: 25531-1).
        - Moving on, 1980; SR-7635; Covington, Gloria. (Box 15)
        - Candy., 1979; SR-7678 (Box 15)
          Durations on labels; words to songs on container.
          Mercury: Manufactured by Phonogram
        - Saturday night special., SR-7679 (Box 15)
        - Ghosts, 1981; SR-7680; Comateens (Musical group) (Box 15)
          Cachalot
        - Just can't help myself (I really love you), 1980; SR-7681; Common Sense (Musical group) (Box 15)
          B.C. Records
        - Blogodo, 1982; SR-7682; Compagnie cre¿¿ole. (Box 15)
          Carrere
        - C'est bon pour la moral, 1982; SR-7683; Compagnie cre¿¿ole. (Box 15)
          Carrere: Zagora
        - Vive le douanier Rousseau!, 1983; SR-7684; Compagnie cre¿¿ole. (Box 15)
        - Compagnie Creole, 1976; SR-7685; Compagnie cre¿¿ole. (Box 15)
        - Comateens., 1981; SR-7686-7687; Comateens (Musical group) (Box 15)
          Cachalot Records
        - Fascinated, 1986; SR-7688; Company B (Musical group) (Box 15)
        - Commodores., 1977; SR-7689; Commodores (Musical group) (Box 15)
        - Lou Courtney; Buffalo Smoke, 1976; SR-7690; Courtney, Lou. (Box 15)
        - Better part of me., 1980; SR-7691 (Box 15)
        - Bill Cosby is not himself these days, rat own, rat own, rat own., 1976; SR-7692; Cosby, Bill, 1937- (Box 15)
        - Funky and tough, 1977; SR-6951; F.A.T. (Musical group) (Box 16)
          Bold Records
        - Straight up, 1975; SR-6957; Exit 9 (Musical group) (Box 16)
          "Not for sale."
          BRC
        - Magic disco machine, 1975; SR-6959; Disc-o-tech (Musical group) (Box 16)
        - Loving explosion, 1974; SR-6960; Eliminators (Soul group) (Box 16)
        - Rumours, 1977; SR-6963; Fleetwood Mac (Musical group) (Box 16)
        - Something new, 1983; SR-6966; Fearless Four (Musical group) (Box 16)
        - Damn Sam the Miracle Man and the Soul Congregation., 1970; SR-6973 (Box 16)
          Tay-Ster
        - Static; Funk will flow, 1996; SR-6992 (Box 16)
        - Earth, Wind & Fire, 1971; SR-7008; Earth, Wind & Fire (Musical group) (Box 16)
        - Foxy live., 1980; SR-7010 (Box 16)
          Dark Horse Records
        - Just the way you like it, 1981; SR-7025-7026; EU (Musical group) (Box 16)
          Infinity Records
        - Free live!, 1971; SR-7032; Free (Musical group) (Box 16)
        - Funky punk; Rock to the music, 1979; SR-7033; Dillinger. (Box 16)
          Valdene Records: Distributed by CBS Records
        - Jungle Jezebel, 1982; SR-7034; Divine, 1945-1988. (Box 16)
          "O" Records
        - Time is running out, 1978; SR-7035; Eddie and the Movements. (Box 16)
          Trucker Man Records
          U.S. Virgin Islands
        - Funky Broadway, 1967; SR-7050; Christian, Arlester. (Box 16)
        - Nassau Day; Midnight plane, 1978; SR-7052 (Box 16)
        - Direct Current., 1979; SR-7061; Direct Current (Musical group) (Box 16)
          TEC Records
        - Doctor Jackyll and Mister Funk; On the slick side, 1979; SR-7072-7073; McLean, Jackie. (Box 16)
        - Love money, 1981; SR-7074-7075; Funk Masters. (Box 16)
          Tania Music; Siamese Records
          Plainview, New York
        - Time is right!, 1977; SR-7093; Gemini Brass. (Box 16)
          Geffen Records
        - New York strut; Feeling, 1977; SR-7100; Fist-O-Funk Orchestra. (Box 16)
          File Records
        - Beat escape; Catwalk, 1981; SR-7101; Fingerprintz (Musical group) (Box 16)
          Virgin Records
        - Break it down; That's how we do, 1990-1999; SR-7103; DJ Boobie. (Box 16)
        - Obeah, the witch woman; You make me feel this way., 1979; SR-7113 (Box 16)
          Konduko
          Florida
        - Universoul people, 2002; SR-7116; Low Tone Priority. (Box 16)
          White label. Promotional copy. Matrix etching side A: L5+ PoM TR; side B: L5+ PoM TR.
          Mahogany
        - Uncle Jam wants you, 1979; SR-7125; Funkadelic (Musical group) (Box 16)
        - Songs of new nations, 1964; SR-7129; De Paur, Leonard. (Box 16)
        - Born ya!, 1976; SR-7132; Equals (Musical group) (Box 16)
          ICE
          Trinidad & Tobago
        - Relax your body, 1989; SR-7136; D.F.X. (Musician) (Box 16)
          Full Moon/Epic
        - Makossa man., 1973; SR-7143; Dibango, Manu, 1933- (Box 16)
        - Tasty jam., 1981; SR-7160-7161; Fatback (Musical group) (Box 16)
          Spring Records